So, when I write code,
所以当我写代码时
sometimes I make mistakes.
有时候我会犯错
Honestly, this happens to everybody,
说实话每个人都这样
even the most experienced programmers.
甚至是最有经验的程序员
Fortunately, pretty much all programming languages
幸运的是所有编程语言
have mechanisms for detecting our mistakes,
有检测我们错误的机制
and letting us know about them by displaying error messages.
并通过显示错误消息让我们了解它们
Error messages not only draw our attention to the problem,
错误信息不仅引起我们对问题的关注
but they also often give us information to help us diagnose the issue and fix it.
但他们也经常给我们提供信息 帮助我们诊断问题并解决问题
For instance, Python will display an error message that
例如  Python 将显示一条错误消息
tells you what line an error occurred on,
告诉您发生了什么错误
and what kind of error took place.
发生了什么样的错误
You'll see a message such as name error,
您会看到诸如名称错误之类的消息
or syntax error, and it'll always come with a line number.
或者语法错误 它总是会有一个行号
Now the line numbers aren't always entirely correct.
现在行号并不总是完全正确
Sometimes they're off by one or two,
有时候他们会被一两个人关了
but they're usually a really good guide to
但他们通常是一个很好的向导
where to start looking for the error in your code.
在哪里开始查找代码中的错误
Up next, we have a piece of code that has a number of bugs in it.
接下来 我们有一条代码 里面有很多虫子
As you work with this code,
当你使用这个代码时
you'll fix the bugs and the line numbers on
你会把虫子和线号修好
the error messages will guide you to just where you need to put your attention.
错误消息将引导您进入您需要关注的地方